const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What auspicious day was Fred and George Weasley born?',
      answers: [
        'February 3rd, 1978',
        'April 1st, 1978',
        'October 23rd, 1977',
        'October 31st, 1978'],
      correctAnswer: 'April 1st, 1978'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'In the book Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, how did Harry get the idea of using Gillyweed for the second task of the Tri-Wizard Tournament?',
      answers: [
        'Neville goes to Harry and gives him the idea of using Gillyweed after reading Magical Water Plants of the Mediterranean',
        'Dobby steals Gillyweed from Professor Snape and gives it Harry after overhearing a conversation between ‘Professor Moody’ and Professor McGonagall about its uses',
        'Harry reads the Magical Water Plants of the Mediterranean and obtains Gillyweed from Professor Sprout',
        'Cedric Diggory tips off Harry about Gillyweed after Harry helped him with the first task'],
      correctAnswer: 'Dobby steals Gillyweed from Professor Snape and gives it Harry after overhearing a conversation between ‘Professor Moody’ and Professor McGonagall about its uses'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the all-female Quidditch team founded in 1203?',
      answers: [
        'Appleby Arrows',
        'Holyhead Harpies',
        'Montrose Magpies',
        'Bulgarian National Quidditch Team'],
      correctAnswer: 'Holyhead Harpies'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'What was Nymphadora Tonks’ original patronus before it changed into a wolf?',
      answers: [
        'Jack Rabbit',
        'Kangaroo',
        'Fennec Fox',
        'Doe'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Jack Rabbit'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'Both of Hermione’s parents had what occupation in the Muggle World?',
      answers: [
        'Family Law Lawyers',
        'Dentists',
        'Anesthesiologists',
        'Mail Carriers'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Dentists'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'Which Harry Potter film(s) did Peeves the Poltergeist make an appearance?',
      answers: [
        'The Sorcerer’s Stone and The Chamber of Secrets',
        'The Sorcerer’s Stone',
        'The Prisoner of Azkaban',
        'None'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'None'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'Who is the creator of the Sectumsempra spell?',
      answers: [
        'Tom Riddle',
        'Severus Snape',
        'James Potter',
        'Bellatrix LeStrange'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Severus Snape
    },
    
    {
      question: 'Which Weasley sibling never had an acting scene in the Harry Potter films?',
      answers: [
        'Charlie Weasley',
        'Molly Weasley',
        'Bill Weasley',
        'Percy Weasley'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Charlie Weasley'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'In the Goblet of Fire, Hermione founded an organization named S.P.E.W in response to the injustices she saw in the treatment of house-elves. What does S.P.E.W stand for?',
      answers: [
        'Society for Protecting Elves at Work',
        'Spell Protection for Elves working for Wizards',
        'Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare',
        'Super Powered Elves at Work'],
      correctAnswer: 'Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'What does Dumbledore says he sees when he looks into the Mirror of Erised?',
      answers: [
        'He sees himself holding a pair of thick, woolen socks',
        'He sees himself with his siblings, Ariana and Aberforth',
        'He sees himself winning the battle against Voldemort',
        'He sees himself eating a Bertie Bott’s bean that is not booger flavored'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'He sees himself holding a pair of thick, woolen socks'
    },
    
    
    ];